Gerry Mulligan Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-148, 160)
  - Song for Strayhorn
    - Score for 2nd movement (orchestra), Tom Fay arrangement; On folder: Ref. 1/17/1987 (Box-folder 141/2)
    - Sketch score (orchestra), On folder: Sketches for revised score of Mvt II, 1/17/87 (Box-folder 141/1)
    - Parts (miscellaneous), On folder: Quartet trumpet parts, originals (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Parts for 3rd movement (orchestra), On folder: Eng. hrn, bass, clarinet, harp for Song of Strayhorn and Rocker Stuite-mvt. 3 (Box-folder 76/1)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 76/2)
    - Parts for 2nd movement (orchestra), On folder: Ref. 1/17/1987 (Box-folder 75/2)
    - Parts for 2nd movement (orchestra), On folder: Parts, including quartet parts (Box-folder 76/1)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet, New version (Box-folder 23A/16)
    - Lead sheet, Laid in: lead sheet for "Pastoral - by the river" (Box-folder 8/11)
  - The song is ended
    - Score (big band with vocal), Lennie Neihaus arrangement; Inscribed by Mel Tormé; On folder: Songwriter's night (Box-folder 135/6)
    - Score (big band), GM arrangement for the Claude Thornhill Orchestra (Box-folder 146/5)
    - Score (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 117/5)
    - Parts (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Parts (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Songs in the key of life, Stevie Wonder
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Songwriter's night with Mel Tormé
    - Lyric sheets; lead sheets; program notes; set lists, On folder: w/Mel Tormé, songs: Here I'll stay, No one but me; All the things, Pick yourself up, Lush life, I'll be around, Mack the knife, Till the clouds roll by, Speak low; Laid in: setlists for Kennedy Center, May 29, 1982; Carnegie Hall, 1981-1982; San Diego, June 3, 1982; Atlanta, undated; Baltimore, undated (Box-folder 53/1)
  - Sorta kinda
    - Parts (big band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95 (Box-folder 47/1)
  - South to a warmer place, Alec Wilder
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Sphinx
    - Sketches; lyric notes (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Splendor in the grass, David Amram
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/28)
  - Spring frolic
    - Score, For Dublin Radio Eire, 1970 (Box-folder 57/2)
  - Spring is sprung
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Spring samba, Gary McFarland
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Spring wings, Pat Williams
    - Score (orchestra) (Box-folder 146/6)
  - Springville, John Carisi
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/11)
  - St. Val's dance
    - Lead sheet, At top of page: On Funny Valentine's Day (Box-folder 20/18)
  - Stable mates, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Standstill
    - Lead sheet, Criterion Music Corp., 1957 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Stardust
    - Score; parts (septet), Bob Haggart arrangement (Box-folder 53/3)
  - Step lightly, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Stomp, Larry Coryell
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Storyville story
    - Lead sheet, Criterion Music Corp., 1957 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - The straight life
    - Lead sheet; parts (sextet), Note in GM's music library: Never used (Box-folder 53/5)
  - Street corner blues, Other title: Goodbye John
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Strike up the band
    - Part (solo baritone saxophone), Note in GM's music library: From Glasgow (Box-folder 21/12)
  - Subconscious-lee, Lee Konitz
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/6)
  - Sublee, Lee Konitz
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/6)
  - Suite
    - Score (orchestra), Luca Fancesconi arrangement; Laid in: note regarding cassette recording (Box-folder 90/3)
  - Suite for baritone saxophone and orchestra
    - Scores (orchestra) (Box-folder 70)
    - Score; parts for 1st movement (Box-folder 77/1)
    - Score with annotations (orchestra), On folder: Mulligan Medley (formerly "Suite for bari saxophone and orchestra") (Box-folder 76/3)
    - Score for 1st movement (orchestra) (Box-folder 69/2)
    - Score for 1st movement (small band), On folder: Revised for L.A. (Box-folder 69/4)
    - Score for 2nd movement (orchestra) (Box-folder 69/3)
    - Parts (for small band, no bass part), On folder: Revised for L.A. (Box-folder 69/6)
    - Parts for 2nd movement (small band), On folder: Revised for L.A. (Box-folder 69/7)
    - Parts for 3rd movement (small band), On folder: Revised for L.A. (Box-folder 69/8)
    - Parts for 1st movement (orchestra), On folder: Original (Box-folder 71)
    - Parts for 2nd movement (orchestra), On folder: Original (Box-folder 73/1)
    - Parts for 2nd movmement (orchestra), On folder: Revised (Box-folder 73/2)
    - Parts for 3rd movement (orchestra), On folder: Revised (Box-folder 75/1)
    - Parts for 4th movement (orchestra), On folder: Original (Box-folder 74)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Revised (Box-folder 72)
    - Part (solo, Mulligan melody) (Box-folder 69/1)
    - Sketch (piano part) (Box-folder 69/5)
  - Sul-fed-gee-o, Gale Madden
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Summer music, Dave Brubeck
    - Parts (bass, piano, guitar) (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Summer song
    - Part (baritone saxophone part) (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Summer's over
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 148/3)
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Finnegan arrangement for the album Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 117/4)
    - Score (vocal sextet), For the "Take six" vocal group (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Finnegan arrangement for the album Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Lead sheet; lyric sheets, Lyric sheets by Judy Holliday (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Sun dance
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Mitchel Forman arrangement (Box-folder 146/1)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, piano), GM personal performance parts (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Mitchel Forman arrangement (Box-folder 35/5)
  - Sun in Aires
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 145/7)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Misc. (original) parts for new CJB (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Sun on the stairs
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Tom Boras arrangement
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Revised parts, second version, 1988 June 19 (Box-folder 125/2)
    - Sketch (for intro), On folder: New intros in progress (Box-folder 140/7)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Tom Boras arrangement (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Original (short) version, playing parts (Box-folder 85/2)
    - Parts, On folder: Quartet trumpet parts - originals (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Parts (rhythm section and solo) (Box-folder 58/3)
    - Parts (extra baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Sunday Mahler
    - Parts (Synclavier), On folder: 4 part, file in "F" (symph) (Box-folder 67/6)
  - Sundown flight, Mitchel Forman
    - Lead sheet; notes; part (tenor saxophone) (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Sunny side of the street, Jimmy McHugh
    - Parts (trumpet, tenor saxophone, clarinet, piano), 1951 November (Box-folder 56/8)
  - Suppertime, Irving Berlin; Al Cohn arrangement for the Holliday with Mulligan album
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 117/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Sweet and slow, Fats Waller
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Al Cohn arrangement (Box-folder 122/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Al Cohn arrangement (Box-folder 32/7)
  - Sweet William, Other title: Neo darlin'
    - Score (big band), On title page: Jan 19, 1981; On folder: For Count Basie (Box-folder 136/7)
    - Parts, Alto saxophone 1 part is missing (Box-folder 57/4)
  - Swing house
    - Score (big band), On folder: For Kenton (Box-folder 133/10)
    - Parts; sketch; published score (big band), On folder: For Kenton (Box-folder 51/3)
    - Parts; sketches (Box-folder 56/11)
  - Synclavier ideas
    - Short scores for "Octnul" and "Nustrngl" (Box-folder 20/13)
  - Tailor
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 42/3)
  - Take five, Dave Brubeck
    - Part (baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 82/1)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Take ten, Paul Desmond
    - Lead sheet; notes on lyrics (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Takin' a chance
    - Score; parts (tentet) (Box-folder 113/1)
  - Taking a chance on love, Vernon Duke
    - Score; parts (tentet), On folder: Tentet for Rebirth of the cool (Box-folder 136/3)
    - Score; parts (tentet and rhythm), Arrangement for the Gil Evans Orchestra, based on tentet chart from 1966 August 23 (Box-folder 136/1)
    - Score (tentet) (Box-folder 139/7)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Parts (Box-folder 66/5)
  - Tangerine, Johnny Mercer
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Tango Milano No. 2
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Tango Potenza Picena No. 3
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Tarde em itapoan, From the 1994 recording Paraiso
    - Lead sheet with lyrics (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Tarry tune
    - Parts (Box-folder 68/9)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Tarrytown
    - Lead sheet, "Idol gossip" variations (Box-folder 23A/18)
  - A taste of blues, John Murtaugh
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Dated: 6/16/61 (Box-folder 119/3)
  - Taurus moon
    - Score; parts, From "Synclavier" folders (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Part (soprano saxophone), GM personal performance part (Box-folder 116)
    - Sketch score; "chorus rejects" (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 123/8)
    - Lead sheet, From "Brasilian collection" folder (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Parts, On folder: Small band trumpet parts (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; sketches (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Sketches; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 34/3)
  - Telethon ride for Bob
    - Score (printed counterpoint, ensemble) (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Score (printed counterpoint, ensemble) (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Tell me when
    - Parts (trumpet, trombone, baritone saxophone, tenor saxophone, piano, bass, guitar), Lyrics in the hand of Judy Holliday; Includes lyrics for "If you don't mind" and "What do you want for your birthday?" (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Sketch (Box-folder 58/7)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Tender woman, Dave Brubeck
    - Part (baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Tenor blues
    - Sketches; lyrics notes, Titles: Sphinx; Milano; Word to the wise; Tenor blues; New shoes; Do you know what I see? (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Tentet - Prestige
    - Miscellaneous parts, Titles: Have you met Miss Jones; Opener; Kaper (George); Bweebida Bobbida; On folder: Prestige; some parts, Parker w/strings; [see also folder 62/2] (Box-folder 62/4)
  - Thelonious Monk
    - Printed collection (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Theme for Jobim
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 128/1)
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance parts and bass part (Box-folder 116)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet, From "Brasilian collection" folder (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: Brazil Stuff, To Jane Duboc (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Lead sheets with lyrics; part (baritone saxophone), For the 1994 recording Paraiso (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: GM tunes/lead sheets, returned by Dave Brubeck, May 1984 (Box-folder 82/2)
    - Lead sheet with lyrics (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/10)
  - Theme for Luv, From the 1967 film Luv
    - Sketches (Box-folder 57/1)
  - Theme for Trambeme, Jimmy Hamilton
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, bass), Britt Woodman arrangement (Box-folder 58/5)
  - There are knives
    - Part (baritone saxophone part) (Box-folder 82/1)
  - They say it's wonderful, Irving Berlin
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: Recording 4/94 (Box-folder 24/6)
  - Thinking of Jobim
    - Sketch scores, On folder: Also "Fred Astaire Strut" as a new tune (Box-folder 131/9)
  - This is the time, Roger Kellaway
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/16)
  - A thought for the day, Manny Albam
    - Part (baritone saxophone), On folder: Wilder winds concert, bari saxophone solo parts (Box-folder 81/4)
  - A thousand clowns
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Lyric sketches, Lyrics in the hand of Judy Holliday (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Through a glass darkly
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/20)
  - Thruway
    - Score (big band), On folder: Arr. for concert with Duke (Box-folder 132/5)
    - Parts (big band), Trumpet 2 part is missing; On folder: For Doc Severinsen "Tonight Show" (Box-folder 48/2)
    - Parts (big band), On folder: Scored for Duke (without "Thruway" tune), original parts (Box-folder 52/3)
  - Thursday's theme, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Time enough for dreaming
    - Sketches, From "Misc. works, some for Count Basie Band" folder (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Tin tin deo, Dizzy Gillespie / Chano Pozo
    - Part (alto saxophone), In caption: Jazz America (Box-folder 58/7)
  - Tis autumn
    - Score; parts (big band), On folder: For Elliott Lawrence, vocal key of "F" (Box-folder 131/5)
  - TNT
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95 (Box-folder 47/3)
  - Tomorrow
    - Parts (piano, bass, guitar, vibes), Found with "The real thing" folder, but not noted in GM's library (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Too marvelous for words, Richard Whiting / Johnny Mercer
    - Score; parts (big band), On folder: For Elliott Lawrence Series (Box-folder 131/4)
    - Score (big band), On folder: For Kenton, 2/52 (Box-folder 133/7)
  - The touch, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - The trap
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Billy Byers arrangement (Box-folder 146/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Billy Byers arrangement (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Lead sheet, From the 1977 film La menace (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Tribute, Simon Pilbrow
    - Lead sheet, Note in GM's music library: Some good tunes from an Australian (Box-folder 22/24)
  - Truth
    - Part (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Turn left on Monday, Alec Wilder
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Turnstile
    - Score (octet), On folder: "Songbook" album, sax section score by Bill Holman (Box-folder 135/7)
    - Parts (octet), On folder: Saxes arr. "Mulligan Songbook" album (originals) (Box-folder 56/2)
  - Turntable
    - Sketches, From "Misc. works, some for Count Basie Band" folder (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Twelve to go, Simon Pilbrow
    - Lead sheet, Note in GM's music library: Some good tunes from an Australian (Box-folder 22/24)
  - Two for the dildo
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 26/3)
  - Two for the road
    - Parts (orchestra), On parts: Arr. Dick Hazard; Note in GM's music library: Arr. Bob Brookmeyer (Box-folder 82/4-5)
  - Two G's [i.e. Gerry Mulligan and Gerry Niewood]
    - Parts (quintet), For quintet recording with Gerry Niewood; Laid in: miscellaneous parts, notes on "Tape marked GM 5," tune lists with timings and notes (Box-folder 65/4)
  - Undecided
    - Parts (sextet) (Box-folder 140/4)
  - Under a star
    - Sketch scores (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 127/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Parts (quartet trumpet part), On folder: Quartet trumpet parts - originals (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Parts (septet), For the recording Little big horn (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/27)
    - Lead sheet, From "Brazil stuff" folder to Jane Duboc (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/15)
  - Underneath a pale blue moonlight
    - Score and parts, For the 1995 recording Dragonfly (Box-folder 140/9)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 20/16)
  - Unexpected places, Johnny Mandel
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/5)
  - Untitled
    - Carriage House Date lead sheets (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Parts (transposed baritone saxophone), On folder: Incomplete file as of 4/16/91 (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Parts; studio notes; schedules, For Ray Wright, Eastman, 1973; Laid in: lead sheet for "Sengali" (Box-folder 59/1)
    - Lead sheet (Feb, 1993), On folder: "New songs for quartet 2-9-93, originals" (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Untitled, Tom Boras
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Useless waltz, Bob Brookmeyer
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 17/6)
  - Utter chaos
    - Sketch; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 25/3)
  - Venezuela 123 - Flying
    - Scores; lead sheets; sketches (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Venus
    - Parts (horn) (Box-folder 56/10)
  - Venus de Milo
    - Score (octet), On folder: "Songbook" album, sax section scores arranged by Bill Holman (Box-folder 135/7)
    - Score (nonet) (Box-folder 129/7)
    - Parts (woodwinds, guitar, bass, drums) (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Parts (tentet) (Box-folder 111/3)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Parts (miscellaneous) (Box-folder 160/5)
    - Lead sheets; bass part (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Via Portofino (Octet of Seacliff)
    - Scores; sketches; parts (octet) (Box-folder 104/1)
    - Score; parts (octet), On folder: Score (I, II, III) new versions (2/5/88) (Box-folder 104/2)
    - Score (octet), On folder: Score (I, II, III) new versions (2/5/88) (Box-folder 144/2)
    - Score (octet), On folder: Orig. pencil scores, new version (2/5/88) (Box-folder 106/4)
    - Score; sketches (octet), On folder: Sketches for revisions (Box-folder 144/3)
    - Score; parts - Part 1 (octet), On folder: New version (2/5/88) (Box-folder 104/3)
    - Score; parts - Part II (octet), On folder: New version (2/5/88) (Box-folder 105/2)
    - Score - Part II (octet), On folder: In progress, new version (2/5/88) (Box-folder 106/3)
    - Score; parts - Part III (octet), On folder: New version (2/5/88) (Box-folder 105/4)
    - Parts - Part II (octet), On folder: New version (2/5/88) (Box-folder 105/3)
    - Parts - Part II, B and C (strings) (octet), On folder: New version (2/5/88) (Box-folder 105/4)
    - Parts - Part II (octet), On folder: New version (2/5/88) (Box-folder 105/1)
    - Parts (octet), On folder: Parts I, II, III used at Freeport 2/7/88, new version (Box-folder 106/1)
    - Parts (octet), On folder: New version (2/5/88), 2nd copy (Box-folder 106/2)
  - Vines, From the 1977 film La menace
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Lyric sheets (Box-folder 54/1)
  - A visit to a small planet
    - Sketches; notes (Box-folder 18/13)
  - Vomini
    - Part (baritone saxophone solo) (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Waiting for words
    - Lead sheet, Note in GM's music library: Mulligan tunes given to Sergio Bardotti (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Walk on the water
    - Sketch scores (Concert Jazz Band), Note in GM's music library: Outchorus sketches, rejects (Box-folder 124/3)
    - Sketch, On folder: Melody for sax soli (Box-folder 67/9)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 35/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Part (baritone saxophone), GM personal performance part (Box-folder 116)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: Quartet trumpet parts - originals (Box-folder 66/7)
  - A walk with Brahms, Earlier title: Milano
    - Score (orchestra) (Box-folder 143/1)
    - Score (rejects), On folder: Rejects, pop symph arrangement (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Formerly "Milano"; playing parts as of the Nat. Symph. 6/13/86 (Box-folder 84/3)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Working parts as of 6/28/1986; Laid in: Australian Pops Orchestra parts list, 3/1/1989 (Box-folder 91/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Working parts as of 6/28/1986 (Box-folder 101/2)
  - Walkin' shoes
    - Score; parts (tentet), From "Gig books" (Box-folder 112/8)
    - Score (tentet), On folder: Original tentet chart (Box-folder 139/9)
    - Score; part (bassoon), On folder: Arr. John Dankworth, May, 1989 (Box-folder 101/1)
    - Score; parts (orchestra), On folder: Rochester Phil., 5/19-20/1989, arr. John Dankworth; Laid in: program and notes (Box-folder 144/4)
    - Score; parts (orchestra), On folder: Rochester Phil., 5/19-20/1989, arr. John Dankworth (Box-folder 108/3)
    - Score; parts (tentet), Baritone saxophone part is missing; On folder: Rebirth of the cool (Box-folder 62/10)
    - Score; parts (tentet), On folder: Tentet revised May, 1992 (Box-folder 138/5)
    - Score of new intro; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: For Kenton (Box-folder 52/2)
    - Parts (big band), Horns parts are missing; On folder: For Kenton (Box-folder 51/2)
    - Parts (trumpet, tenor saxophone, bass, drums) (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Parts (big band), On folder: For Kenton (Box-folder 133/9)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 109/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Orchestral score parts, arranged by GM, 2/15/91 (Box-folder 109/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: GM arr. 2/15/91; orchestral score parts - complete (Box-folder 109/4)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 109/5)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Rhythm section parts, arranged by GM, 2/15/91 (Box-folder 109/3)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Part (trombone, incomplete), From "Standards" folder; Includes sketches for "Soft shoe," "Bernie's tune," "Darn that dream," and "Motel" (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Lead sheets; drum part, On folder: From the published "Mulliganettes" series (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Lead sheets; lyric sheets, Lyrics by Gerry Mulligan, Bobby Troupe, Mel Tormé (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Waller-in